http://www.riverbendtf.com/privacy-policy/

×
Request Your Free BrochureTimber FramingCustom Timber HomesCommercial ProjectsTimber Frame BarnsTimber ChurchesHybrid Timber HomesPost & Beam HomesFloor PlansPhotosKitchen & DiningGreat RoomsBeds & BathsLoftsEntry & StairsOutdoor LivingCommercialOur ProcessesPerfectFit™Custom DesignYour PlansFabricationStructural Shell IllustrationOur ValueA Team of ExpertsDesign to BudgetEnergy EfficiencyBuilding SystemCraftsmanshipAwardsWhere We BuildUnited StatesCanadaInternationalAbout UsFAQsHome Planning SeminarWebinarsBuilders & ArchitectsContact UsEventsBlogMedia Room
Architects & BuildersBlogAbout UsEventsContact UsRiverbend Brochure 888.486.2363
888.999.4744Custom Timber FramingCustom Timber HomesFarmhouse StyleMountain StyleMidCentury StyleCraftsman StyleBarn Home StyleEuropean StyleCommercial ProjectsTimber Frame BarnsTimber ChurchesHybrid Timber HomesPost and Beam HomesFloor PlansPhotosKitchen & DiningGreat RoomsBeds & BathsLoftsEntry & StairsOutdoor Living SpacesCommercialOur ProcessPerfectFit™Custom DesignYour PlansFabricationStructural Shell IllustrationOur ValueTeam of ExpertsDesign to BudgetEnergy EfficiencyStructural ShellCraftsmanshipAwardsWhere We BuildUnited StatesCanadaInternational
Menu
888.486.2363Search our Site...
×
Menu
888.486.2363
Privacy PolicyPFB Custom Homes Group, LLC is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to all websites of PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC and governs data collection and usage. By using the PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC websites, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC includes, but is not limited to, the following brand names: PrecisionCraft Log & Timber Homes, Riverbend Timber Framing, M.T.N. Design, TimberScape Outdoor Living Structures, Point Zero High Performance Homes, Rustic Architecture, and Elegant Wood Homes.Collection of Your Personal InformationPFB Custom Homes Group, LLC collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, or telephone number when you provide it via a form accessible from one of the PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC’s websites. PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests, and favorites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses. This information is used by PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC websites.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the blog post comment section of the PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC websites, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC does not read any of your private online communications.PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC encourages you to review the privacy statements of the websites you choose to link to from PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC so that you can understand how those websites collect, use, and share your information. PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC and the PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC family of websites, including, but not limited to: PrecisionCraft Log & Timber Homes, Riverbend Timber Framing, M.T.N. Design, TimberScape Outdoor Living Structures, Point Zero High Performance Homes, Rustic Architecture, and Elegant Wood Homes.Use of Your Personal InformationPFB Custom Homes Group, LLC collects and uses your information to operate the PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC websites and deliver the services you have requested. PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC and its affiliates. PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC does not sell, rent, or lease its customer lists to third parties. PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is NOT transferred to the third party. In addition, PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC does not use or disclose sensitive personal information you may provide, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC keeps track of the websites and pages visited within PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC websites, in order to determine what PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC or its sites; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC, or the public.Use of CookiesThe PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC websites use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience and to better understand from where our clients originate. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC pages, or register with PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC site or services, a cookie helps PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC features that you customized.The email programs of PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC employs some tracking methods. PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC tracks “opens” via a tracking pixel in the email – meaning the company tracks who opens e-mail messages and when the e-mail messages are opened. The “clicks” are tracked via encoded URLs – meaning whether you click on the links contained in our e-mail messages is tracked. This information is used internally only to help PFB Custom Home Group, LLC deliver relevant messaging, and is not shared with any third parties.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC services or websites you visit.Analytics ToolsPFB Custom Homes Group, LLC uses analytics tools and other third-party technologies, such as Google Analytics and Bing Analytics, to collect non-personal information in the form of various usage and user metrics when you use its online sites and/or services. These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, MAC Address, mobile unique device ID, and other similar information.The third-party analytics companies who collect information on the PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC websites and/or services and other online products and/or services may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.In addition to PFB Custom Homes Groups, LLC’s use of technologies as described herein, the company may permit certain third-party companies to help it tailor advertising that they think may be of interest to you based on your use of the PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC’s websites or services, and to otherwise collect and use data about your use of PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC’s websites or services. For more information about this practice, please see the “Third Party Advertising Technologies” section below.Advertising & Third Party Advertising TechnologiesPFB Custom Homes Group, LLC uses your information, including personal information, behavioral metrics, geo-location data, demographic data and marketing preferences to personalize and display advertisements, and other content for you.In addition to using cookies and related technologies as described above, PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC also may permit certain third-party companies to help it tailor advertising that they think may be of interest to users, and to collect and use other data about user activities on its sites and/or services (e.g., to allow them to tailor ads on third-party services). These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior. These companies may use information about user behavior in order to provide customized advertisements across various services and products. In the course of providing these services, products or placing advertisements, these third-party companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer, and may record information to these cookies based upon your activities on any of PFB Custom Group, LLC sites and/or services, and on third-party websites. Each of these companies uses this cookie information according to their own privacy and security policies. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out as indicated in this Policy. Please note this does not opt you out of being delivered advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.Security of Your Personal InformationPFB Custom Homes Group, LLC secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to This StatementPFB Custom Homes Group, LLC will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC is protecting your information.Contact InformationPFB Custom Homes Group, LLC welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC has not adhered to this Statement, please contact PFB Custom Homes Group, LLC at info@pfbcustomhomes.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Need More Information?Whether you’re looking for more information or would simply like to learn more about us and our services, don’t hesitate to contact us. Please follow the link below to access our online form or call us at 888.486.2363 in the US or 888.999.4744 in Canada. We look forward to hearing from you.
Order Riverbend Brochure
Contact Us
